<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>


	<!-- ■Ｔシャツ -->
	<HAR_NM_Tshirt.label>T-shirt (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_Tshirt.label>
	<HAR_NM_Tshirt.description>A T-shirt designed exclusively for Nearmare. It's eerily similar to that worn by humans.</HAR_NM_Tshirt.description>

	<!-- ■学生服 -->
	<HAR_NM_Sc_Uniform.label>School Uniform (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_Sc_Uniform.label>
	<HAR_NM_Sc_Uniform.description>A school uniform worn by Nearmare when in civilized space. It seems to be catching on... Makes you feel like a student, increasing learning speed.</HAR_NM_Sc_Uniform.description>

	<!-- ■袖付きシャツ -->
	<HAR_NM_SShirts.label>Long sleeved shirt (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_SShirts.label>
	<HAR_NM_SShirts.description>A long sleeved shirt just like humans wear. Provides more protection than a T-shirt.</HAR_NM_SShirts.description>

	<!-- ■深夜のドレス -->
	<HAR_NM_BDress.label>Black Evening Gown (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_BDress.label>
	<HAR_NM_BDress.description>A revealing jet black dress worn by Nearmare nobles. Intended for aristocratic use, it's not crafted with defense in mind.</HAR_NM_BDress.description>

	<!-- ■白夜のドレス -->
	<HAR_NM_WDress.label>White Evening Gown (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_WDress.label>
	<HAR_NM_WDress.description>An elegant, pure white dress worn by Nearmare nobles. Intended for aristocratic use, it's not crafted with defense in mind.</HAR_NM_WDress.description>

	<!-- ■チャイナ服 -->
	<HAR_NM_China.label>China Clothes (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_China.label>
	<HAR_NM_China.description>A traditional garment custom made for Nearmare. Easy to move in, increasing movement speed.</HAR_NM_China.description>

	<!-- ■メイド服 -->
	<HAR_NM_Maid.label>Maid Clothes (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_Maid.label>
	<HAR_NM_Maid.description>Servant clothing worn by Nearmare to curry favour with powerful individuals. Feeling like a maid increases work efficiency.</HAR_NM_Maid.description>

	<!-- ■夜魔の軽装 -->
	<HAR_NM_DLArmor.label>Night Demon's Light Armor (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_DLArmor.label>
	<HAR_NM_DLArmor.description>Nearmare battle gear. Quite revealing, but projects an energy field for defense.</HAR_NM_DLArmor.description>

	<!-- ■夜魔の呪装 -->
	<HAR_NM_KArmor.label>Cursed Armor (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_KArmor.label><!-- Bit of a liberty here, but this really doesn't translate well (lit. Night Demon's Cursed Clothing). Part of me wonders if this is intended to be Night Demon -> Nightmare -> Nearmare pun-->
	<HAR_NM_KArmor.description>A special equipment made for Nearmare, developed by a sect that used to study them. It provides poor defense, but enhances the senses, allowing for more precise movements.</HAR_NM_KArmor.description>

	<!-- ■着物 -->
	<HAR_NM_Kimono.label>Kimono (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_Kimono.label>
	<HAR_NM_Kimono.description>Traditional attire custom-made for Nearmare. Difficult to move in, but such elegant attire makes a good impression during diplomacy.</HAR_NM_Kimono.description>

	<!-- ■巫女服 -->
	<HAR_NM_Miko.label>Shrine Maiden Dress (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_Miko.label>
	<HAR_NM_Miko.description>Traditional attire custom-made for Nearmare. It is difficult to move in, but makes a good impression and is comfortable in a variety of climates.</HAR_NM_Miko.description>

	<!-- ■一枚布 -->
	<HAR_NM_Itimai.label>Wrapped Fabric (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_Itimai.label>
	<HAR_NM_Itimai.description>A large piece of cloth wrapped around the body, too primitive to call clothing.</HAR_NM_Itimai.description>

	<!-- ■ブラウス -->
	<HAR_NM_Blouse.label>Blouse (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_Blouse.label>
	<HAR_NM_Blouse.description>A lovely blouse for fashion-conscious Nearmare. Easy to make and comfortable to wear.</HAR_NM_Blouse.description>

	<!-- ■ライダースーツ -->
	<HAR_NM_RiderS.label>Riding Suit (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_RiderS.label>
	<HAR_NM_RiderS.description>A strictly functional riding suit, eschewing unnecessary ornamentation. Provides minimal protection from both attacks and weather, but is easy to move in. Originally worn by motorcycle riders.</HAR_NM_RiderS.description>

	<!-- ■ナース服 -->
	<HAR_NM_NurseS.label>Nurse Attire (Nearmare)</HAR_NM_NurseS.label>
	<HAR_NM_NurseS.description>The costumes worn by women involved in medical care. It inspires benevolent intentions in those who wear it, lowering combat-related abilities while improving surgery-related abilities.</HAR_NM_NurseS.description>
	
</LanguageData>